LAN DAO

(510) 289-7492 Idao@millikin.edu

PROFILE

Diligent, flexible learner with strong leadership and a passion for web and app development. Open minded and highly motivated student with study and internship abroad experiences. Proficient in Vietnamese, English, and working knowledge of Russian.

EDUCATION

Millikin University Fall 2018 – May 2022

Decatur, IL, USA

- Bachelor of Science in Information Systems and Computer Science
- Cumulative GPA: 3.766/4.0

EMPLOYMENT

International Student Specialist, Center for International Education

Aug 2019 - Present

Decatur, IL, USA

- Organize and implement International Orientation each semester for more than 50 incoming students
- Keep records for more than 150 domestic study abroad students annually
- Assist the office with office and filing duties including, but not limited to, emails, presentations, formal letters, and phone
 calls

Math Enrichment Program Tutor, Millikin Math Center

Sep 2018 – Present

Decatur, IL, USA

Assist walk-in students with solving math problems in various topics

Data Analyst Intern, Center for International Education

Apr 2020 - Jun 2020

Decatur, IL, USA

- Assessed the data collected through 3 international programs to identify trends, successes, and areas of improvement
- Set up Study Abroad Pre-Departure Orientation remotely using online platform for students to prepare for their exchange program
- Hosted 2 virtual sessions to address concerns and questions for 50 international students

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCES

Guest Speaker, American Association of University Women Luncheon

Feb 2020

Decatur, IL, USA

- Delivered a speech to 30 audiences about Vietnam, personal experience adjusting and adapting to the US lifestyle
- Addressed the importance and spread awareness about gender equality as well as women's role in the Vietnamese society and worldwide

PROJECTS

Developer, budgetify (GitHub)

Sep 2020 - Present

Develop a mobile application for iOS devices that keeps track of monthly transactions

Developer, HoverXchange (GitHub)

Jul 2020 - Present

Co-develop a Google Chrome extension that converts currency amounts on mouse hover using current exchange rates

Software Inventory Consultant, Mari-Mann Herb Co., Inc.

Aug 2019 - Dec 2019

Decatur, IL, USA

 Collected and analyzed data on the company's local machines to solve the software-related issues and come up with recommendations for the client

AWARDS

Freshman Outstanding Student Award, Tabor School of Business

May 2019

SKILLS